good afternoon everyone
and now it's time for our
uh for our fourth question of today
uh you know so it's our fourth question
today so
uh i hope that many of you had
participated
in the first second and third questions
also
as it would have been fun you know it's
really nice
because we are giving your awareness
about what we can do
and with these little questions we can
learn
a lot uh good afternoon everyone i am
adrika and now we will be starting
with our fourth question so
here we have our fourth question
of the day on the screen
so let's uh quickly discuss
what the question is so you witness a
motor crash
as a passer by how will you help the
victims
a and then your options are a it is
risky to help
b help the victims irrespective
of the outcome c you ignore the victims
d blame this uh blame the system
so so this is our
fourth question of today so you all can
participate
uh you all can participate in these
questions
and become a part of making india
off and become a part to make india
safer on indian roads
as you know all what we are discussing
all these questions
uh they are helping they are helping
many of us gain awareness
about how we should how our behavior
should be there
on the roads so
uh so what is the price so
uh these are the price we will be
getting every two hours the person who
gives the right our answer they will be
getting these prizes
uh every uh you know uh after the answer
this two hour each question is valid for
two hours
so uh the prices in this you can
uh choose uh either a bike safety kit
for
your family or a car safety kit for your
family
so you can participate become a part
and win these prizes uh
as and they are also helping us know
that
why uh it is important and
uh you know how how we can
how we can get these prizes it is very
simple we just have to answer
this question i'm repeating it again for
all of you
you witness a motor crash as a passer by
how will you help the victims a
and the options are a it is risky to
help
b help the victims irrespective of the
outcome
see you ignore the victims d
blame the system so
this is the question which uh you all
can answer
and it is really simple and really
easy to answer this question you just
simply
uh have to see there's a link in the
description
you can either use that to answer or you
can answer it from our youtube
page or from our facebook page also so
it's really simple you know it's really
nice that
every two hours you will be getting a
question
and you can answer this you know the
results you will be getting
at 10 at 10 pm every day
who are the winners and what was the
actual answer of this question
so you know every two hours an anchor is
coming
and telling us about the question and
with the help of the link or from our
facebook page or from our youtube page
also
you can simply answer this question
and then you can make sure that
everyone is safe you are also safe
and others are also safe so basically
by participating in this you become a
part
uh you just become a part uh in making
indian roads safer you know
uh all of us we all use indian roads
every day either as a pedestrian or
as a driver uh you know we all
use roads every day no matter of what
age we are no matter
in which uh no matter how we are you
know
we all use indian roads every day
so uh you know millions of us use this
every day and 415
people die on indian roads every day
so uh you know as we know that
uh these roads they are a thing which we
all use uh and like you know men
most of us i'll say all of us use these
roads every day
but it is not the safest way like
uh people use roads but it might be
possible that they do not use
air to travel or they do not use the sea
route to travel
but all of us are using these roads
every day uh every day
but still these roads are not the safest
and to make them safer uh
and to make them safer we need awareness
and uh and to become a part
of making these roads safer you can
simply answer this question
and then we also will be having other
questions
as well every day we have five questions
which
all of uh all of you can answer
uh you know so however today we have our
topic as road safety
as i just discussed that all of us use
indian roads every day
but 400 and people die on these roads
you know it might be that we do not use
the air to travel
but at the end of the day all of us
uh you know no matter which type of
family we live
where we live uh we we all
are using roads but still these roads
are not
safe and that is why we have to make
these
indian roads safer and
make sure that everyone is safe
you know we are also safe and others are
also safe
like if we take a small example uh
of like over speeding which many people
do
and this causes many crashes also
so uh you know why do people
over speed because they do not know that
what its outcomes can be uh
you know because over speeding like many
a times
uh what happens that these little things
like
over speeding or drink and drive these
things
with this you are not only causing the
harm to yourself
you are also harming other people you
are
also harming other road users as well
and that is why it is important that we
follow
all the traffic rules because they are
for our own safety
you know not for children but for
but for everyone's safety for our own
safety
like if we take a small example
of people wearing helmets or seat belts
so many times what we see is that people
like if someone is not wearing their
helmet
and they see a traffic police then they
just quickly wear their helmets because
they think that
then they will be getting a chill on but
we shall not follow these things for
children we should be following
these things for our own
safety for our own life because if we
are not following these road safety
rules if we are not
following these traffic rules we are
risking
uh somehow we are risking our own life
and that is why not for children but
for ourselves so
we just discussed that why uh
that what happens on these roads every
day
so what we can do to change this
situation
what we can do to make sure that
no more people die on indian roads
every day so we can just start by
a small thing and that is
to start following road safety rules
you know no one will change suddenly
but if they will start it one day then
uh you know within a month or within two
to three months
they will learn that how to drive safely
uh you know or if you are a pedestrian
then you will learn
that how uh how i can be
safe on the roads how i can
i should be correctly uh crossing the
road
so these things we all can do
and uh you know
so so you all can participate in this
question
and uh i will just request you all to
participate in the next question
as well uh you know each question uh it
comes
all the questions they come every two
hours
so uh so i will request all of you to
participate in the
in these questions because uh at the end
of the day
at 10 pm every day we have a show called
bluntly speaking
there you will get the results as well
as answers
and with those answers and results
uh you should learn we all should learn
that what we can do
like we have today's questions so
this we can uh so with this
we should learn that what i should do
so these small little things they can
save
everyone's life and with this simple
step
uh with this uh simple step like it
doesn't even take
uh it doesn't even take five minutes it
just takes less than that
to just simply answer this question
and then you can answer this question
and
uh you know you can tell others also to
answer this
uh so uh you know you can answer this
question as well as the other questions
uh which will be coming today uh as well
so so you know
making indian roads safer of making sure
that no more people die
on indian roads and for that we are we
have decided to drive
safely
[Music]
and then you can answer this one also
and the other one also you can also try
the previous ones if you have not tried
yet
uh so you know this with this little
question we will uh become aware
about many things
road safety
[Music]
so i will request you all to
this question for the last time now so
it is that you witness a motor crash
as a passer by how will you help the
victims
so your options are a it is too risky to
help
b help the victim irrespective of the
outcomes
see you ignore the victims d blame the
system
so basically the question
answers
[Music]
i will request you all to please try
this
question
so thank you so much everyone
you